{
    "subject": "resource/Blue_Seed",
    "predicate": "property/englishtitle",
    "object": "Lost & Trembling on a Trip to Michinoku",
    "human_readable": "The English title of Blue Seed is 'Lost & Trembling on a Trip to Michinoku'.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9068215489387512,
            "question": "What does 'Lost & Trembling on a Trip to Michinoku' refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8349208235740662,
            "question": "What is the English title of Blue Seed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7838144302368164,
            "question": "What genre might 'Lost & Trembling on a Trip to Michinoku' suggest for the story?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4093409776687622,
            "question": "Where does the story of Blue Seed take place?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3994688093662262,
            "question": "What is the main plot of Blue Seed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34165510535240173,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the characters in Blue Seed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33927956223487854,
            "question": "Are there any themes explored in the story of Blue Seed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32525449991226196,
            "question": "Is Blue Seed an English anime or a Japanese anime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3246573507785797,
            "question": "Does Blue Seed have any other translated titles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2646245062351227,
            "question": "What is the original Japanese title of Blue Seed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The English title of Blue Seed is 'Lost & Trembling on a Trip to Michinoku'.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3023_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Blue Seed have any other translated titles?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3023_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Blue Seed an English anime or a Japanese anime?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3023_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any themes explored in the story of Blue Seed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3023_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3023_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3023_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3023_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3023_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3023_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3023_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3023_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3023_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3023_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3023_76.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "The triple to evaluate is \"The English title of Blue Seed is 'Lost & Trembling on a Trip to Michinoku'\".\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: According to the documents provided, the English title of Blue Seed is not \"Lost & Trembling on a Trip to Michinoku\". Instead, it mentions that Blue Seed is an anime series based on Yuzo Takada's manga and provides some plot details and production information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"no\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}